	
60th anniversary Altiplano watch, 43 mm. Case in 18K white gold. Dial with hour markers in 18K white gold. Sapphire crystal case back. Manufacture Piaget 1200P, ultra-thin automatic mechanical movement. Limited edition of 360 individually numbered timepieces.	Watch G0A42105	23900	
60th anniversary Altiplano watch, 34 mm. Case in 18K white gold set with 72 brilliant-cut diamonds (approx. 0.52 ct). Dial with hour markers in 18K white gold. Manufacture Piaget 430P ultra-thin hand-wound mechanical movement. Limited edition of 360 individually numbered timepieces.	Watch G0A42100	28500	
Possession earrings in 18K rose gold set with 16 brilliant-cut diamonds approx. 0.25 ct	EARRINGS G38PY800	2850